'''
1. See ex24.py
2. See ex25.py
3. See ex28.txt
4.
 a. https://stackoverflow.com/questions/156767/whats-the-difference-between-an-argument-and-a-parameter
 		Parameter is a variable in method definition, arguments are the data passed
 		Parameter: variable in declaration of function
 		Argument: value of actual that gets passed to function
 b. Python Docs: https://docs.python.org/2/library/string.html
 		See string_method.png
 		To Lowercase = "String".lower()
 		To Uppercase = "String".upper()

5. Write a Python unction that takes a user input as an integer and check the numer is prime or not.
 a. Hint: A prime number (or a prime is a natural number greater than 1) and that has no positive divisors other than 1 and itself.

 6. Write a proram that does a conversion for the user. Your program should give user the following option to select from. Once the user selects the option and enters the input, your program should do the conversion accordingly.

 a. Convert from kilobytes to bytes
 b. Convert from mega byte to bytes
 c. Convert from terabyte to byte
 d. Convert from terabyte to megabyte
 	i. For Example:
 			Press 1 to convert from Kilobyte to byte
 			Press 2 to convert from megabyte to byte...
